(this.webpackJsonpquiz=this.webpackJsonpquiz||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,n){},14:function(e,t,n){},15:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var o=n(0),a=n.n(o),s=n(3),r=n.n(s),c=(n(13),n(4)),l=n(5),i=n(1),u=n(7),m=n(6),h=[{question:"React is _______",answers:["Module based","Component based","Both of above","None of above"],correct:2},{question:"As soon as the state of react component is changed, component will",answers:["Does nothing , you have to call render method to render the component again","be created again from scratch","re-renders the component","None of above"],correct:1},{question:"We can go for ______ when there is possibility that our user could change the data?",answers:["Keys","Ref","Both","None of above"],correct:1},{question:"JSX is typesafe?",answers:["True","False","None of the Above","Cannot Be Determined"],correct:1},{question:"Keys are given to a list of elements in react. These keys should be -",answers:["Do not requires to be unique","Unique in the DOM","Unique among the siblings only","All of the Above"],correct:3},{question:"ReactJS uses _____ to increase performance",answers:["Original DOM","Virtual DOM","Both 1 & 2","None of the above"],correct:2},{question:"In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?",answers:["setState","render with arguments","props","PropTypes"],correct:3},{question:"What is ReactJS?",answers:["Server side Framework","A Library for building interaction interfaces","User-interface framework","None of the Above"],correct:2},{question:"State in react is________",answers:["Internal storage of the component","A permanent storage","Both of Above","None of the Above"],correct:1},{question:"Everything in React is a _____________",answers:["Module","Component","Package","Class"],correct:2},{question:"React merges the object you provide into the current state using which of the following",answers:["setState()","State()","getState()","None of the Above"],correct:1},{question:"Arbitrary inputs of components are called?",answers:["Keys","Props","Elements","Ref"],correct:2},{question:"_____ can be done while more than one element needs to be returned from a component?",answers:["Abstraction","Packing","Insulation","Wrapping"],correct:4},{question:"Which of the following needs to be updated to achieve dynamic UI updates?",answers:["State","Props","Components","None of the Above"],correct:1},{question:"Lifecycle methods are mainly used _____",answers:["To keep track of event history","To enhance components","Free up resources","None of the Above"],correct:3}],d=(n(14),function(e){Object(u.a)(n,e);var t=Object(m.a)(n);function n(e){var o;return Object(c.a)(this,n),(o=t.call(this,e)).reload=function(){o.setState({score:0,show:0,selected:0,count:180}),o.showQue(0)},o.showQue=function(e){clearInterval(o.myInterval),o.setState({question:h[e].question,options:h[e].answers,correct:h[e].correct,que_no:e+1}),o.myInterval=setInterval((function(){o.setState((function(e){return{count:o.state.count-1}}))}),1e3)},o.nextQue=function(){var e=o.state,t=e.selected,n=e.correct,a=e.score,s=e.que_no,r=e.total;t===n&&o.setState({score:a+1}),s===r?o.setState({show:2}):(o.setState({selected:0,count:180}),o.showQue(s))},o.chosen=function(e){o.setState({selected:e})},o.Start=function(){o.setState({show:1}),o.showQue(0)},o.state={que_no:0,total:h.length,score:0,selected:0,show:0,count:180},o.showQue=o.showQue.bind(Object(i.a)(o)),o.chosen=o.chosen.bind(Object(i.a)(o)),o.nextQue=o.nextQue.bind(Object(i.a)(o)),o}return Object(l.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this,t=this.state,n=t.que_no,o=t.total,s=t.score,r=t.question,c=t.options,l=t.count,i=t.selected,u=t.show;return l||(2==u?clearInterval(this.myInterval):this.nextQue()),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},0===u&&a.a.createElement("div",{className:"s0"},a.a.createElement("h1",null," React Quiz "),a.a.createElement("ul",null,a.a.createElement("li",null,"A sample quiz on react."),a.a.createElement("li",null," total 15 que will be here."),a.a.createElement("li",null," maximum of 3 minutes is allowed for each question.")),a.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary btn-lg",onClick:this.Start},"Start Quiz")),1===u&&a.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-lg-12 col-md-10"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"que"},a.a.createElement("h4",{className:""}," Question ",n,"/",o)," ",a.a.createElement("span",{className:"timer"}," Time left : ",l," seconds "),a.a.createElement("p",null," ",r," ")),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer"},a.a.createElement("ul",null,a.a.createElement("li",{onClick:function(){return e.chosen(1)},className:1===i?"chosen":""},a.a.createElement("span",null,"A"),a.a.createElement("p",null,c[0])),a.a.createElement("li",{onClick:function(){return e.chosen(2)},className:2===i?"chosen":""},a.a.createElement("span",null,"B"),a.a.createElement("p",null,c[1])),a.a.createElement("li",{onClick:function(){return e.chosen(3)},className:3===i?"chosen":""},a.a.createElement("span",null,"C"),a.a.createElement("p",null,c[2])),a.a.createElement("li",{onClick:function(){return e.chosen(4)},className:4===i?"chosen":""},a.a.createElement("span",null,"D"),a.a.createElement("p",null,c[3])))),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"submit"},a.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary btn-lg",onClick:this.nextQue},n===o?"Submit Quiz":"Next Question")))),2===u&&a.a.createElement("div",{className:"que"},a.a.createElement("p",null," You have completed the quiz. ",a.a.createElement("br",null)," You got: ",a.a.createElement("strong",null," ",s," ")," out of ",a.a.createElement("strong",null," ",o," ")," questions right."),a.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary btn-lg",onClick:this.reload},"Restart")))}}]),n}(a.a.Component));Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));r.a.render(a.a.createElement(a.a.StrictMode,null,a.a.createElement(d,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))},8:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(15)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.509e830d.chunk.js.map